Hello, thank
to Elastique to us
this evening.
So, thank
to the accue
bienveillance of
the Home Sweet
Company in your
local spectaculare.
We have a new
view on
all right,
it's a
great great
David,
the incarnation
of the community
Elastic
on Earth.
So,
thank
again a
David for
these meet-up
or it's
always the
bonner
to intervene or
to participate.
So I'm
I'm Van Monnier,
I'm at
at the
Chab Vision
at chapter I
and I'm
Louis
Jordan,
engineer I
at Chavvysion
also.
It's my
manager.
So we're
so we're
a subject
that we
expect to
you're interested
is the
management of
a manager
conversational
with Elasticsearch
So,
so you know,
you know,
we're
we're members
of Chabvision,
Chavision,
it's a group
of tech
who agglomer
of the
companies of
different
horizons and
and who they
they're
organized,
each one of
the
companies
are acquies
for a
self-affair
particular.
So we
were
in the
Colone
Coam,
that's
it's
Acqued for
the NLP
from the NLP.
So,
after the
competition
continued.
then,
then
we're
so
we're probably
about
1,
000,
well
and not
200 million
of
Chies of
our
activity in the
Regalian
and in
the
companies,
so
a
a part of
or a
or more
equal,
and we
we're
member of
chapter I
so
the chapter I
what's
is,
is that
that's
that in the
group
there are
they have
have
their
capacity
agentic
there,
and there
and then
there
there are
and then
they want
to
they're
they're to
to
for our job to
for
what we
called the capabilities
and the capacity
to the capacity
structure
to access
to access to the
yeah.
So we
are we
members of
the squad
text
analytics because
there's
there are
people specialized
in the
text,
there are
specialized
in the
image and
the
vision by
or
there
there are
specialized in
audio.
So there
there
so there
soads,
so we
fundissons
we
our
little
solution
a
a solution, and
that is packaged
and is a
light,
and so it's
to provide
it's to provide
even to
evene
at the client
that
regalian that
that could
interest
so it was
it's the
good
time
it was really
the
time
was simple
it's
the
knowledge
base
so
so Quam
had been
on
on this
so much
the knowledge badge
which is
what is the
the
principle
for had
a
mass of
non-structurated
essentially
of the text, you
you
add
the dimensions
and
the NLP,
each
dimension
is a
visualization
in a dashboard,
and you
expect, in
you
baladad
of
dimensions
to
see what
what
is what
see an
information,
you
will explore
what
they're
these aggregates,
so
so the
data-d-d-
-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-
-d-d-d-
exploration-d-d-
of-d-d-d-
-exploration, or
exploration
of relations.
So, you
you'll have
find the aggregates,
and then you
will be bad
what you'll
be able to
not be able to
not
to be able to
see what you
know of
a new
society,
and then you
if you
see you
not the
you'll
see it's
the
way to
know of a
word,
in two
more, in two
mo,
it's,
of
millions of
documents
without
having
to have
so,
it was
the
whole
index
of
relation,
so I was
put a little
a little george
you'll
will be in
the bar
right,
you'll
see that this
will
go
it's
going to
the
long of the
so
so it's
it's
so that's
bn-25,
and then you
you're
talking about the
exploration of
relations,
then after
after we have
the relations
between the
entities,
we can
pass,
we can't
pass, we,
so you can't
an analysis
bottom-up
or top-down,
bottom-up,
part-up, you
of the
relation,
then you're
trying
to
fill to come to come to
or you're
in fact, you're top-down,
you're parted to
the mass, and then you
use, you
bring a
thing, you
go to
do the drill down,
so that's
so it's
we're in a
second index,
we have our
two index,
so we've said,
we're not
not moving in
LP,
so we have
many
of the
, we have the
capacity to
have the
ability to
know,
the NLP,
we said,
we're
we're part
for the
we're parted
year, you've
so you've been
in fact,
the idea
was the problem
is that
the problem is that
the same,
and the
that's
the roadmack that
we're
that's
before,
so,
so it's
it's
with the
LLM,
then the LLM,
and it's
well,
but
you have
access to
the only
only way
to communicate
with an
LLM
is,
so it's
to say,
how
I'm
how I'm
going
to put
my
data
in the
project,
so it's
all
the idea
of
the
and then
rag,
and then the
many many, the
model
multi-modo
are
coming,
for
to say,
that the
in fact,
the
documents that
were
in the
old
text,
it's
terminated,
so it's
all the
documents
office
like
but now,
but now
we
we're
add
the audio,
we
add out
the video,
in
fact,
the
models
are capable
for
an
image
for an
image,
if you
have
a video
of
you
transcri
an audio,
If it's
the video, we
transcri the audio,
we detect the
scenes,
we
take an image of
each
scene and we
decry
each one of
the
scenes of the
image,
so it
does
so it's
transformed
in text,
in fact.
The RAG
is
good, but
you
pose
a question
to
and then
then the
dialogue is
a
little
course,
good, so
it's able to
interact with your
data,
so
we don't
don't necessarily
on
the agent
conversationalal
and especially
that the
rag
is not the
sole
tool that
you're
to use,
it's a
that is a
like when you
make a
conversation,
for
to respond
to respond to
your
question,
we're
using a
tool,
and the
Rague
is not the
the
first tool.
It's the
first
the first
there's
for the
base
structural for the
and then
there
there are 50
other
typically
the tool
that used
all
David,
pardon.
So,
it's good,
but
they're
construct
faste
easily.
So,
So, in fact,
have
to take
tools that are
simple,
and they're
assembled
in super tool.
So,
so you have
two
ways to
do it
do you know,
it's a
bit like when
when you
have a
team,
we're not
not
team
that's a
team that
works, so
so,
so there
is specialized
in the
launch the
cuto,
the
other,
he has
he has launched
the cord,
the other,
he is in
the combat, he
in
a combat manu,
the
other is the
fire at 200
meters,
you have assembled
your
team, and then
then you
have been in fact,
it's
you're in fact,
you're
to get to
when the
guy is
and the
air air is
arrived, it's
it's quite
barred,
so it's
how you
you're
orchestrate the
the
equivalent of your
team.
and so
so you
do you
have a
thing that
that's
the workflow,
and we'll
it will be
it's the
whether all the
editors go,
all the
people who is
in the
course,
that you are
there
is the agent
multi-orchestray,
so typically you have
all you've all
used Clod.
So Claude, typically
it's a system
agentic.
You use today
a system
like
CHAPGPT in
line,
in fact,
it's a system
multi-agentic
multi-orchestraceed that
you have in fact.
So it's
to apply that
to the enterprise
to your
own own own
own own
to perturb the
plan of
retrait of Yvan,
we can
can't say
that the
arrival of
2022,
2022, 2003,
has kind of
very
bolversed the
world
of the
logiciel
and
and not
these
PME
startup.
It's that
we had
an
scheme
quite
where the
client
came
with
his
data and
the
work
of
the
startup
tech
was to
they
were
to
them
in an
insight,
in
information
supplementer
that
had
to
help
their
to
make their
and
but
now.
before
we had
a
back-end
with
which
who stocked
the
data
the client
who also
also
effect
and
and a front-end
with
the
with the
users
were
interact
in
in 2022,
we're
a new
new
actor
potentially
intelligent
which is the
LLM
that
and the
and all
the
question that
all
the
companies
in the
tech actually
is,
where is
do
place
on this
on
so
why they
they are
there
you are
the
suite
elastic
today
is just
just a
merveveay
but
But they're
they're
don't
do
to be
it's
complicated,
tordue,
there's
all the
things that's
it's
certainly
non-dermies,
it's
that year
that's a
LLM
that you
do not always
what we
and so you
have
two times
different different
so different,
so the
so,
so, so
why,
why we're
doing,
all people
we said,
it's
very complicated,
so it's very
very complicated
I would
I'll confirm, but in
fact,
what we've
got our chance
is that we're made
it at the
beginning of the
beginning of course,
it's
a year that
that's a
idea that
that was
that's
the
naive rag,
and that's
that's
working with
Elastix
Seet
because we
geted
at the
time,
I mean,
the post
on
Elastic
on the
capacity
to introduce
the
embedines
that came
to come
to get to
geted that.
so
it's
it's not
not very
not very long
we're
not very
what, but it's at the
time,
so we've
had put the problem
at the beginning,
so that's
it's a
the second thing,
is many people are
on the cloud,
many of
solutions are
at base
of the LLM in
line, and our
clients,
you've seen,
as we've had an
an activity
regalian,
in fact,
the regalian,
it's on-premise,
it's on the
machine,
and it's
deconnected of
internet.
So,
how how
how can
do that in
internet,
the market is
more restrain.
And the
second
other thing,
there's
there's very
A problem of framework, the problem
of the framework, is
that you make two
and the thing
that's
it's amazing, that's
it's very good,
it's just
merrilyue, the problem
is that if you
have the
things that you
do you do you have
a hack,
then you're doing
a second, then
then a three
and then you
upgradeed,
all your
, there are a
one of course
that you
might have
or you
have been, or you
have
you're obliged
to let's
because because
it's all
and you
finishs
by, you
finish by
functioned
with
the points
of
febleness due
due to
who are
dissemined
and you have
to have
all you've
could have
put to make
to make
functioned.
So that
we've
with the
chain
at the
it was
it's
the
hand
index
also
and
the
engraph
is
the
problem
of the
framework
is a
problem
and a
problem,
especially
our
clients
are
equipped
they're
they're all
they've all
all
always
to
berer
an
LLM
They've
they've
they've had a
little
bit
a bit of
and they've
have used
for example,
of a chat
conversational
on
in a
middle of an
application
that they're
they've
have used
to make a
place,
and a
so
so that's
so much,
so it's
in fact
it's
they're
and they
they're going to
and make
to make
in a
way of a
where they're
access to
the idea of
the
LLM
on
content
I have my LLM
that are
who are
and I'm
to connect
to my
content to my
content to
so for
so,
so we're
so
we're
we're trying to
a problem
that is the
context,
it's
that is
that
the language human,
we've
at a
pretty at
about 200,
to make
to make up
the
point, the
the system
of
the language,
it's a
connection
series,
you
you're
and the
words
are
after
after the
and you
all after the
quite
it's
quite it's
it's quite
and so you
can't
you can't
you're able to
you're quite
limited.
So,
the humanity
has made
many years of
a year,
has arrived, but
it's
with the language, and the
language, and the
idea
general, is to
say,
I have a
context,
there,
okay,
so I,
so I've
I've
used the
same
things than you,
the same
things, and you're
also, you have
you have used
the same
things,
and so, and
when I'm
to
I'll
understand
the
minimum,
but you
will
be able,
of our
context,
reconstitue
the other
other
side,
problem is
we're
getting to
get to
machine
to the
other
side.
So,
in fact,
the
context
change,
and
it's
to
reproduce
this
phenomenon
with
a
machine.
And so
we've
connected
the
Rago
to
don't,
so
we,
talk with
an
interaction
natural,
So with a language
language natural,
I pose my
question in language
natural and I have
a response
in language
natural.
We've
we've seen that
we can
do it
with an
LLM, the
first version
of the
GPT
3-5
you did,
you have the
possibility to
to communicate
with an
LLM
with a prompt.
So,
all the idea
of
Rague,
to
be
to be
get to
bring
the
content of
your
data in
in the
Fenetre
of
context.
So,
for you
have
a
bit of
It's to say
the
chain
is considerably
rallonged
and it has
it had
in fact,
when you
have
you have
integrated
your
documents
office,
have been
extracts.
So it's
so it's
the OCR,
if your
documents
are numerized,
if
if they're
don't know,
will be
have to have
there's
they're
decry,
and if you
have you
have
the
transcription,
of the
audio.
Then you
have
then you have
don't
which are
these
fichies
text or
gizons
or x-emel,
that's
which are
which contain
all the
data
of your
document.
Okay.
so they're not
in the
they're not in the
language,
it
you have
in fact,
in the
group we have a
chance
to have
six strands,
so
which is
the leader
of the
translation
offline,
which has
80 pairs of
language,
pardon,
so we
can't
then,
and then
then they're
also,
I've
you've
of the entities
name
and they're
to navigate
in it in
and add
to addote
the dimensions.
And so
the
new thing,
is that it
is that you
have
now,
like the
rag
does
function
that's
by the
invention,
that's
the invention of
Micoloff
who
Google, who
has encoded
the
phrase in vector
and the
idea of
and to
say,
I'm
being encoded
in
an
space
of a
dimension
124 or
other,
I'm
the space
vectorial,
there's
to say,
if the
phrases are
like
that,
they'll
not
say
the
same
if the
vector
is parallel
in
this
space,
in
my
phrase
is
parallel.
So it
would
make a
way
simple
to
to calculate
if
if a
phrase
is parallel.
And
the vector
associated
to the
phrase is
parallel,
the
phrase
does
mean
the same
thing
so.
So,
so that
it's
applied
by
elastic
that
on the
last
for
relations,
do
stockage,
Elastique,
fact,
when the
embelings
have
fleurried,
base
vectorial
have
proliferate,
okay,
but
elastic
is
alligue,
and
like
it's
an
functionality
elegant
and
well
made
and you
will
see,
it's
quite
to make
make
in
up
and
certainly
that it's
compatible
with the
B.25,
the
score that you
have
in
embellinin
is the
same
that is the
the
you have in B.M.
it is compatible.
So that's the
thing just
dingh, in fact,
because we'll have
to have
the interest of that.
My
little George,
there's a
new
new,
an new
index
that's
appeared,
the
and so the
the interest
now,
it's
opened a
rag
that's a
very
more more
more performant.
Why?
Because, because
because
before the
B.
B.25,
we say,
it's an ancient,
it has an
an enormous
advantage,
the BN.
It's that
he is
focus
on the
the terms
the
most
significant
of your
request
that will
bring the
terms the
most
significant
of the
documents.
Okay,
so it
that
respond to
what
about the
the question,
what
do you
not
always
the
semantic
search
where it
will be
on the
sense
of the
question.
So,
the
sense of
question,
what
mean
the
what we're
to
we're
talking,
it's
different
different, so
so it's
important,
important, and it
it's important, and it
document
of chink,
so it will
have to rier rank
so it's a
rinker, so it's a
that we need to
do that
we have to do
boulos.
so we're
now,
we're going to
that's
that is a
that way,
Rabe Rack,
there's
there's a
hybrid,
with a
ronker
in the
I'm in
I'm in the
simple
rag,
so I'm
so all right,
my number
my index is
a
pretty clear,
there's a
plenty of
notions that are
coming in
in the Hector and K&NN,
so it
had come to
it's a
complexified,
and then the
people, the
problem,
is you have
the
people are the
people who are
those people,
they pose
whatever
like what
So,
they pose
these
questions
ambiguous,
so we know,
they're not
what they
know,
they
they pose
questions
in fact
implicit,
that
they're
that they're
that they
imagine that
he's
that's
on the
name,
that is
So, in fact,
the idea
here is to
how I'm
how I'll
can be able
to work
to be able to
arrive
to get to
the
question
foereuse.
And,
in fact,
the idea,
is to have
a
routeer
that
is that
whether my
question
is correct,
if it
is a
bit
implicit
or
ambiguous,
I'm
will be
depropos
in
questions
diverse,
and
I'm
be able
to
let me
other
context,
parallel
to
that,
I have
a
traversed of graph,
because we have
seen, is that the chunk
with the embedding
is it's good,
but it has
only only the
point of
the phrase,
if you have
the notion that's
in
the
door of the
thing that,
in
fact, it's
it's difficult
to
relier,
so it's an
application of
a graph
for
to try to
that's
not long
of one of
the other.
So that
it
gives
we
have
far
re-ranked,
we can
we can't
the
point,
because
we're
limited
with the
type
of
prompt,
and it
we
The first thing is
being
independent of the LLM,
and you don't
you're not with
with a baton
so,
so the idea,
and the idea
and then it's
to have a
response in
language natural.
So if the
subject of
the graph
you
interest,
there are
there
two zoos that
you've
are
known,
it's the
same,
in fact,
it's,
we can
make
that we can
make sure,
the
graph with
elastic,
so that you
there's
another talk,
it was, it
I don't know how
it's it, but,
So the rag,
now if we
we're
repran,
at the
you have
the rag
simple
that you
have
talked,
but if
there
there's
on the
we're
on
every
each
rocket
sub-roquette
part
in
in a
rag
complicated,
that
a rag
simple
again,
so that
so
I'm
re-gues
and
I'm
Chh who are on the Chonk
for the chank, so
all that's
all of Chunk,
so with
Elastic, it's
that's
it's quite,
we're paralleling
the
things, we're
retrieve, it's
really, it's really,
it's really not the problem,
so, so.
So, in fact,
you have,
write your
Pithon, you
can you
you can
you can be
a factor
at a
pretty 10 of
execution between
the time
Piton and
the rocket
elastic,
and then, and
all the
factor of
two,
a little
with your
PITon,
with the
LLM.
So, in
fact,
the Retrieve
is absolutely
not the
problem,
so.
So the,
so the
idea is
to say,
it's
it's good,
the rag,
but I
do my
question,
and plunk,
it's
so it's
how
it's
to say
the rag
is not
not
the tool
of the
to the
have been
using, in
fact, the
function
calling.
So what is
is to say,
I'll give you
give a list
of tools
parami
10,
so
it's
rarely
more more than
and you
describe
each
of your
and you
describe the
task
that you
want to
you
have
in
your
question
and he
will
know
that is the
good
tool that
is,
it?
is
a
method
in
a
language
a language
so
an
point
be a MCP, with the protocol
with the protocol
that is
Esperanto,
but it can
be a method
Pyton,
that's
I know,
and so I'm
a method
of the
argument,
and there are
two sorts of
of parameters.
There are
some of
have you
give you
know,
if you
know
with a
idea,
you have
the URL,
but
but if
if
in
there
there are
elements,
by
example,
METO
at
Boston,
he will
He will
extract
Boston, and he will
say,
and he will
know,
to
get the
air to
the
weather,
and Boston
is
the
argument
of your
function
to
have
make a
it's
a
we're
I'm
going
of
LLLLM,
so
what is
the
first thing is,
first thing you
you
say that's
you're not
not touch with
with a
baton
okay,
grososmodo
we're
of
French,
, we're
under
French, so you know, you
know the problem
of the sovereignty, okay,
so it's a problem
number one for
us, for all
all the European,
and I think there
people have
many people who are the
problem,
to reduce the
dependence
American,
so gross
a LLM,
you have three
choice possible,
or you
go to
you go to
go to the
and you have
you have
understood that
all the LLM, you have
what you're in
what you're
in their part
to the U.S.
U.S.
Submied
to YACT
okay,
so it
so it means
that's
the GEMini
open AI
yeah,
the problem,
is that
economically
and in
performance,
you know,
you'll
never,
that's
economically,
it's always
more
to go to
and in
performance,
would
rarely
rarely have
to have
the
same
performance
that you
don't
that,
so,
so
so that's the
solution
of
facilitation,
okay, okay,
and then
you have
said,
you have said,
Right,
nothing to rent at
at my,
at all the
of course,
everything,
nothing,
and you're
in the
little
and then you're
then you're
I'm doing,
by the
they're probably
, but I'm
going to
get a 48 giga,
okay,
how much I'm
I'm getting
in a rack,
it's
it's two U,
I can
I'm make
four.
A machine
like that
it costs
$35,000
million
the question
is
It's how
how I'm
I'm ready to
to make
$35,000
for having a
time of
response
reasonable for my
users.
You're
you're going to
you're
find you're
with four
if you're
rich,
five,
rack,
have turned
that,
so
there's
and the
people
vealue,
so
so it's
complicated,
it's
cost
so
so much,
it's
a great
thing,
so that's
that's
what comes
at
very, very
very
you say,
I'm going to
I'm a
a gentie
a gentie hoster.
So the solution,
the third
solution,
that's
it's
I'm going to
good,
a
non-souou
European, and I
submised,
and I
take
the models
intermediary
because he
has not
not access to
very
but they can
take
these Guen
32B,
these
Mistral Small
or,
or
these models
of decent,
so typically
they offer
now,
by example,
OVH
the F,
the Fé,
LLLM has a
service, you have
an API, you
pay and then you
use your token,
and you guarantee
that the token
can't
not at the
U.S.
the U.S.
in the U.S.
the L.L.
I'm a
talk, the
the proms
library,
it's
to have
a cruele
to
it's
it's good, it's
pretty, to
get a
to get it,
the tool
factory,
is,
you can
get the
to be
easily
saying,
well,
what's
what you
see,
do the
argument
that I'm, okay, and the semantic memory, he's, he'll
he'll arrive, he'll
a little effect,
and we'll
we'll
you, we'll
explain what's
so it's the.
So,
so you've
got to
finally,
to be able
to have a
conversation
complete with
your agent
I,
is that for
the
instance, the
service to
the
architecture
complicated
that you
have
presented and a
that's
a rag that
function
in one-shot,
you
you've
come with
your
question,
it's
there's
things in
the
cullies.
The LLM,
a
part of an
prompt
well-conce
you can't
the
answer the
to the
question, and
it's
there's
no
notion of
memory with
the
pipeline
of Ragh
that
has
defrayed
LinkedIn
in
2023, and
there's
there's not
transition
between
the Rag
is what
that all
want
and the
experience
chat GPT
that
want the
users,
that
are in
being in
in a
conversation
multi-tour
with an
agent
who
will,
like
the
question,
to
respond
on the
question,
understand and to
think of
and it
and
of the
question
speech of
today
of the
So,
so we're
we're not
in
these
questionements
because
finally,
creators
had
already
had already
this simulation of
a
conversation
between
two
users.
They had
in
their
model
made in
in line
a
format
which is
the
norm
of
all
the
great
creators
of
the
format
open
AI
which
will
stock
a
conversation
So
finally
for
the
epitonista
in the
conversation
format
open
AI is
is
nothing
than
of
a
list of
which
the
chants
don't
have
necessarily
role
so
who is
who
is who
is
the user,
user, the
the
assistant
the agent
I,
what
what has
has
It's
the content,
so the
replica, and
the
agents are
more the
more we have
added
the
change,
so
like
it
explained
Yvon,
we
have used
the
use of the
things,
the function
call,
in the
in these
subchchins
so chisons of
you have
so you have
if you
here, if you
look
in
dictionary
that represents
a tour of
power,
you have
the role,
the assistance
it's the agent
I
who has
talked,
he has
pronounced
no
word
because he
has
decided to
call
the
function,
he
has
decided to
call
the
function
get
current
weather
with
as
argument
Boston
as
locality.
And so
all
is condensed
in
this
great
form
that
all the
providers
of
models
partage
and
they
have
decode
it.
it's
pretty
rather
,
if you
can be
just
It's
very
very good
an object
an object in
an
and an
is easy,
we can
create
these index
with
the object,
the property,
depopage,
of
so much,
it's
it's simple, it
it's just
just to
bring this object
to a
format open and
and an
conversation
on
open and AI,
we
let in
our index
and the
tour is
so away,
so
if it
if it's
so simple,
we'd
would
going to
you
do
hour
this
is
The problem, is that
it's that
it's to implement
a
memory,
it's to
the
issue
is that when
we're
when we
the
question
when we
had
a
with a
with
their
agent,
they
see
pass.
Or,
we can
not
technically
force
necessarily
make
a
question
in
an
entry of an
LLLM.
So,
during
long time,
the limit
was essentially
technically.
It's
a
is that
the LM
have what we
have a
a
fenetre
of context,
so we can
put,
we could make
a certain
number of
tokens in
entry of
the model for
they're
respond and
and
not a
error
500.
So for
those who
have
commenced
the
year
for long time,
the
limit of
context of
a
Lama
was of
8,000
token,
it
represents
a
two
two million
words,
three
pages
of
document Word.
But when
when we
have
a long
conversation
with
our
agent,
model,
especially if he
he
does
call
to
use
the
document,
you
know,
the
window
that
on
premise
is
very
rapidly
saturated.
And
even
today.
these
models
the
most
perform
like
Cloud
Opus
4.5
etc.
we are
on around
200,000
token,
around 50,
60,000
and
if you
you
are using
when you
have
vodododed
too
long time,
he would
compacting conversation,
you
attend
three minutes
before to
have
what
that's
other.
So we're
obliged
to think
make a
mechanism
to
come
compresses
the information
that we
will
make
in entry
the
LLLM
for
to have
the
response
and
continue
the
conversation.
You
say,
okay,
if we
have
some
we have
conversation of
Clod
we're
trying,
you're
you
will
be
pay
because
the
cost
of an
,
and
is proportional to the number
number of
tokens
made in
entry.
So,
it's a
year
with your
conversation with
your
LLM
by API, it
it's
not very
because the
context is
very
you say,
you know,
the
weather
at Boston,
you
have
grieie
20 token
in
doing that
but
you
advance
in the
redaction
in a
report,
you
saturate the
your
centeem
request,
of
your
conversation
and it will
it will
it will cost
it's probably 20
times more
than the
first
and that the
people
people are
quite
so even
it's
to
think to
make
to make
a
to
management
and so
it's
not
so simple
that
if
we're
look
what
we
have
the
framework
which we
have
already
that you
don't
not
in
our
care
and that
that
bring
for
the
language graph
so
that
I
I've
a
it's
that's
that has
changed
that
when
when we
had
when
about about
about
the
we're
on
and
in the
work
as
in the
information,
we're
in
their
library,
in
their
documentation
a
number
of options
for
a
people who
did the
to implemente
implemente
if you
exist
we
we have
the
conversation
buffer memory
memory
tampon.
It means that
your model,
it has 30 K
of token
of context,
and I
then I'm
the 30
and I'm
think it's
on the
what's
you're
doing
you're going to
get to
the
line of
30,000,
but you
have
do
all
you have
I'm
going to
that
will
see
we're
going to
the
in the
talk
and
will
be
a
little
part
you
You
you dine
with
and they pass
all of your
conversation
to you
talk about you
talk about
you're in
half hour of
table.
Then she will
you talk about
one of the
treterer,
then during
20 minutes
of the DJ,
of the
cell,
and then
after you
have kind of
she has
a doubt
and she said,
finally,
is you
sure that I
can place
Jonathan and
Toma
at
a coote
and,
and then
in time
human,
we have
we have the
mechanisms
in our
that we're
that we
will
we've got
to
what we
have said
there
a year
or two
when we're
talking about
the
plan of
table
and
to be
able to
connect
the
and
respond
to
this
question
that.
But if
we
apply
the
method
of the
memory of the
memory
tampon
we
on the
location
of the
sale
and
we
have
no
information
on
the
plan
table
able to
a
question.
so
it's
it's not
and
the
by the
option by default in
the
hand
graph.
Second option.
So,
window
glisting
and the
third thing is
to
make a
resume,
I'm saying,
okay,
I'm
attention,
going to
get a
time
I'm going to
an
LLM
in the
coolis,
I'm
to be
reduce the 30 K
token
in 20K token
and then
then
then,
it's good,
I'm
reparty for
for 20K
token, I'm
tranquil, but
we've
can't even
have been the
granularity of the
formation in
route.
It's a
mean,
maybe in
the whole
conversation,
if we're
having
resumed,
if we're
having two hours
of
conversation with
my
cousin in 30,000
we're
maybe the
last thing
that's
at Noelle
last
Jonathan and
Thomas
was quite
really
raled
and so,
we're
we're able
conserved
kind of
form of
resumet,
we
we've
had used
as
we've had
talked to
Trater,
the
DJ and
and then
had
the granularity of
the
information,
so we can't
still
not
respond to our
question
so that's
not much,
it's always
not really
because
all the
30 K
tokens,
I'm
doing a
LLM
and so
I'm
leads to
this
resum
in MapReduce
for those
who who
who
who am
the
information.
So finally
they have
also
other
implementations,
entity memory,
Conversation,
memory,
they explain
it's very
that it's very
experimental
and that
it's not
not too
it
is
not sure
they're not
the
service
after
Vents.
So we
see
that
the
framework
that
are
going to
and
that
the
problem
propose
these
solutions
to
the
question of
management,
while it
is
very
important.
So,
when
we
are
desesper
we
will
look
what
that
research,
not
this
paper
of
March
which
is
interesting
which is
called
cognitive
architect
for language
agents,
that we
call
Kohala in the
community, and it's
one of the
papers that
has been the
most
cited
on the
question of
the
memory of
agent
IA.
in
fact,
they propose
an analogy
interesting
between the
the
way the
human
function and
that we
would
that our
agent
I
function,
and they
use
and they use
difference
between
three
forms of
three forms of
memory
which
exist
she
the
first
is the
memory
semantic
which
corresponds to what
we know,
the
things that
we've
learned at
the school,
by example,
the date
of the
practice of
the
Boston
was in the
United,
and this
sort of
and that
we can
simulate a
memory
semantic
with
with these
tools like
the
where I
get
connected
my
LLM
that has
with
conessence
parametric
with
speciality,
it's
your
domain
and it's your
different, and
it's the
the
years, it's the
years of master
and you
specialize
on a
subject.
We have
the
memory
episodic
that
correspond
to correspond to
things that
we have
made.
for example,
this
morning,
I'm
up
put my
little
dinner,
I've
worked
and then you
bring the
RER
for
to come
with
great pleasure
now.
and for
for an
agent
I,
corresponds
to
the
actions that
he has
effected,
so
those
he has
launched
before.
Because with
always
this
problem
of
compression,
if
the
a play a
so it's
going to cost, it
will coste
it's an appell
appell of API,
it's
paying, and it's
very suboptimal.
And, and
finally, the
third type of
memory is
the memory
procedural, which
corresponds to
a
some kind of
that we have
ingerer
without
really,
for example,
I know,
know, I can
know
to do
and that,
it's
in doing
instructions
precise in
the system
prompt of
our agent,
that we
will arrive to
give to
these automatism
of reflexion
all along
of our conversation.
So,
with
these
little ruse
technique,
we
see that we
could
try to
give to
our
agent
I,
memory that
similar in
in
this
functionment
that
that's
the
most
possible
of
an
agent
with
who we
have an
of an
conversation.
The problem
of
this
paper
Koala
is that
finally
it's a
paper
that
is a
an implementation
the
bell
things
they're
we're
don't
to continue
and
to
read
other
things.
survey
on the
question
of
the
memory of
information
without
this
page.
I'm
for that you
have
to
the
idea is
researchers and
the
have the
have used
the
different
vac
technological
for
implement
this
memory.
So the
first
memory
of
2022,
repose
essentially
on the research
semantic,
so
techniques
rag-like.
The techniques
of memory of
have been used to
work
on the notion
of the
graph of
memory, with
with
these methods
inspired
of the
psychology,
where we
we
get
written
notes,
at
every time
that
new
information
important
appear
in the
information
and then
read these
notes in a
graph and
after
the
on
this
movement
that
is a
parallel
with
the
popularity
paragraph
in
in 2024, and
we have also
used also the techniques
of memory
which the LLM
chose the LLM
chose it
the information
of the conversation
is important and that
he's
it's written in
an index.
The inconvenience of
this technique
that is that it's
these
tools
supplementer,
it's
these tokens
consummated,
with also the
risk of error
if we
have
to
have used to
something important
or that
we've
written
something of
something.
To always the
same
to
that's just
recently
the
system the
system
which is
illustrated by CloudCode,
where we're going to
write in the file
systems
to the agent has
access with
these
tools of
the information
important in
the
fichies and not
not in
the index,
the base of
data or
or the
graph.
So,
there a
kind of the
panorama
technical
that is
possible to
deploy
for
construct a
memory a
more more
intelligent.
It's
we
had used
in 17 page
we've
had mal
at the
head,
we
we have
presented
plenty of
techniques
and we
know
not too
what
can
maybe
that the
the things
things
simple
are the
major.
If I
recapitual
our
business
technical,
we have
to
get
to get
intelligently
the
memory that
we're
a
mechanism
of
a
mechanism of
on the
object of the
conversation
complete
on
open
and AI,
we
do
operate a
form
of
this
conversation
complete
for
an
for an
MLM
that
he has
a
minimum to
respond to
the
question
to the
finally,
that's
the formulation
technique
of our
business, we're
we're able to
adapt to
dynamically
to adapt it dynamically
to the
height of the
thing of the
context
of the
model
using,
if our
client
has
no problem
to
use
GPT
and
and will
pay for
two
costs,
we
don't
and we
can be in
premise,
my
limit,
32 K,
so
it's
the
constraints
of
the client.
It's also also
to be
to be the
the enchenement
logic
of the message,
so you have
have to have
an notion of
order,
we can't
not have
a rag
simple and just
extracts
the
fragments of
the conversation,
it's
a order
chronological and
and it
can't be
able to
selection
only the
passage of
the
conversations
which are
really
useful to
respond
to respond to
how
implement it
we have
decided
we have decided
to make
a mix
between
many
techniques
proposed, with what we
have called the
memory
a
short term,
which corresponds
to
the last
message
of the
user
because
often the
last question
will
contain
these an
an an
affor
or
references.
So,
by example,
I
I do
a
study on
the
char
in Ukraine,
make
the list
of
in Ukraine
the
last question
and
this on
the
Russia,
this question
that,
it's
sorry,
I'm
sorry, I
have spoiled the
questions
of the
question of
the
And the
last question
does
make sense
that by
the context
immediate,
so for that
it
function,
it's
certainly
that's
the
few
different
messages
for
power
contextualize
the
replica
of the
particular of the
user and
and at
this,
we
complemented
that
by
a
research
of
conversations
the
most pertinent
in the
conversation.
So we're
going to
have
a
kind of
of
rag
with
the
contrains
techniques
that I
have
constraints
are
So,
like
Yvant
you've
you have
to make
the rag,
we
don't
chunk
and we're
don't
decouped
by
phrase,
or
the
replique
of a
conversation
are
an
un-gale
interaction
of
the
message
can just
per
a phrase,
like
if you
have
made
an
explanation
to
your
LLM
that can
make
a
part
so
sofe
the research
semantique
is
effective is
effective
just at
a certain
tie
if you
don't
the
chung
too
is
We
is fosy,
it's fosy,
it's
not.
So in fact,
what we're
going to be
to have
to do,
what is
is a
is quite
to be able to
to apply to
the
content of the
conversation, the
same
the same
treatment that
do you know,
we're
cut in
in a
little phrase.
Do you
few phrases that
we need
in an index
a part,
an index
of a
and a
and we're
going to
not the
replicant
on these
fragments of
conversations,
which we
will
selection
the
more pertinent
by
the
last question of
user, of the
and so we have
a
sort of
where we're in
where in fact,
we're in
the
prompt
to
LLM
for generate
the
step
of the
conversation,
the
key
messages,
the L
messages
the
most
more
than the
question,
and we
have
an
equation
on
the
number of
K
and
of L
in
function of
the
type
of context
which
is
defined by
the
model
that we
use.
So it's
a
method
which is
rustic
by
a
what other
have the other have
been able
implemented,
and that
there's the
advantage of
being
frugal,
scalable,
and that's
made at the
economy,
when we're
even we
use
these
big models.
For you
show you
that we
have absolutely
a
transparency
on our
secret
industrial, and
for those
who
who like
PITons,
want
a little
the
objects that we
have used.
So,
we're
not
stocked the
, in
we're
we can
have
s affranchire
to
the format
open
AI for
redefine
in Elastique
a format
particular
for stock
the conversation.
So we'll
define
a conversation
like having
an
idea unique
and
the information
on the
user who has
launched.
It will
make the
products that
have
in the chatbot
to have
like in
chat
GPT, the
English
and to
navigate
of a
conversation
to navigate from
an
object,
the
fragments
conversationalal,
a fragment
conversationalal
a,
an idea
a ID
that he
has proper,
he has
the information
of the
conversation
to the
he is
attached, he
has the role
in the
role in the
he's
so it's
assistant
user,
he has the
the number
during,
for example,
the conversation
is constitue
of, I
think,
I'm
tours of
the
fragment that
is the
second
fragment
of
13th
tour
of
parol,
by
example.
And the
the
fact of
having
with a
script
Piton
that I
didn't
have
this
this way
the
kindiest
to
do
reconst
a
from
very simple
in the index,
I do the
the aggrega
of all the
fragments
conversational
who have
like
like ID
of
or this
idea that
and I'm
it
and it
can
be
to reconstitue
the object
that I
can
my API to
obtain
directly
the
response
the response
that I
can
do you
get
in indexed
in the
index
and
continue my
conversation
in having
made the
selection.
So that
that has
a
good
that we
force to
create a
new index,
the index
assistant
who will
stock these
fragments
conversationalational
to have
insistants
in bade
in our
products.
So,
like I
said
is a
pretty,
in
terms of
techniques
we
use what?
We
we use
the
rechurch
vectorial
and a
bit of
code
piton
and we
have a
system
robust
escalable.
Other
other
people are
more
more intelligent.
I
refer here
to a
talk
by
the
ancient
president
of Jina
A.A.A.A.E.A.e.
and that
he ported
precisely
on this
question.
So these
slides
interesting
have a
bit,
like I
did
do,
but actualized,
did a
point on
all the techniques
that had
been experimented
for
implement the
memory of an
agent,
with in
plus the
consideration
interesting
of the fact
that
sometimes it's
important
also to
forget.
So in
his toll,
that he has
also
very insisted
on this
importance
to have
selectioned
what
time of
that
and the
case
with the
notion
of
the notion of
decay,
which is
very
interesting.
So for
that
for you
that we
can
do
things
technically
complicated,
that's
a
real
issue
of
research
actual in
intelligence
artificial and
that
Elastique
has
been
that it's
also
a question
on
on which we're, of the
news in the new, so we're coming, we're
So, we're
getting a
agent conversationalal
GPT-like who
function in
other products, but
the people are
never content.
Yeah,
we have
the users,
so the
users, they benn
their fichiers
in which I
want I'm talking to
talk about it
and I'm going to
and then I'm going to
say the JAPT
that,
that the,
a conversation,
I produce,
they produce,
to
many
interactive,
a fischier.
So,
in fact,
it's an
to introduce the
file the
case in the
dance.
So you
do you do you
do you do
do you have
do that, you
know, it's
a bit
that we're doing
that we're
doing that
we're
on the
another problem,
is that we're
we're in a
quantity of
information,
we've
we're
to reduce
to
get to
the
window to
, it's
always the
same
problem.
So,
there's
that's
that
the
user is
using
upload
the
PDF at
wallet in
the chat,
like
you're
doing with chat
GPT,
pose
some
The people who have
a budget
illimited
say,
well,
it's simple,
I extract the text
the text of the
PDF,
I'll make
in the
preempt,
and then
but that.
But
remember you
of our
contract
technique,
is that
if the
the PDF
is 20
page,
it's to
at
about 60,000
tokens,
that my
model
on
30.
That's
not
and it's
how I
do you
do you're
on the
information
that's
only the
more of the
Later,
the user
pose
a question
that's also on
the PDF.
It means that I
mean that I
do I'm
refafffooly
in the
for re-selectioned
only the
information
pertinent for this
new question.
So the question
that is
super simple.
Yes,
this feature
that exists in
chat GPT,
implement it
is easy,
demand of
the
real reflections of back-end.
So,
what's
we do
today in
2025 or
six when
we have a
problem and
we can
not too
where we're
, we
pose the
question at
chat GPT.
So I
I did
I've made
a retro
engineering of
the
functionality upload
of the
fichier and
Canvas
of chat
GPT,
simply
in the
interrogeing
and
and he
knew how
it
functioned
and it
and it's
well.
For example,
learn that
when you
benned
your documents
in chat
GPT,
they rest
in fact the
documents
rest on the
servers
on the server
open AI
around
hours,
it's a
little
and the
conditions
of
not more
clear,
so if
during the
hours and
that you
have
the
chance they
in you repose
you repose a question
on the document,
it exists
again, you
you repassel
the
last, he
it has
used the document
is there,
it's
a lot of
the server, and
we're not
so it
can't
break the
the flow of the
conversation.
Information
interesting.
It's
means that
the
things are
stocked in
in the servers
of Open
AI.
Well, we
we're
going to
stocked
the
we're going to
fichies of our clients, and
it's also
we have
also that
we
have said,
finally, we
finally,
inger
the
fissue of our
and we've got
did with
our ag,
we can do
do it
so we're
we're reproduing
the
same
logic,
and we
have
converted
the problem
of
the
problem of
ingestion
of
online in
a
problem
of tooling.
I'm
explain.
What we
have created a
system
that we
called the
system
of the
system of
artifacts
in
it's
inspiring to
what's
using
Google AdEK
Google
Adj Development
Kit.
So,
that in
in
an index
an space
a part
we
create
with the
name
of the
user and the
ID of
conversations, and
in these
conversations,
we
have stocked
the
fichies that
user
upload at
the
demand and the
fichies
that the
user is
in
trying to
create by
co-construction
with the
assistant.
And in
fact, we
we will
give
tools
that will
can
permit to
to
interact with
with
these
fichies.
So when
the
when the
user
will upload
a
new
a new
file in
live in
the
conversation,
what's
case is the text
is extray, and then we
see the pipeline
of rag that you
know you can't
we can't
the text, we
decoup
on morso, we
make in a
index,
so there we have
a
index a
part, the
index of
the chunk of
artifact,
which will
allow to
it isolet
I
isosos
my rag
that is on
the
conness
generic of
my
fichies
specific that
that I
made for
this
conversation
uniquely.
And in
how the
LLM
will
know that
can have
access to
these
fichier there, is that
that the upload
of the
file is completed
that the
machine has been
been inject in
the
prompt system
the fact that
the user has
uploaded
telf
if if
for example
I upload a
file
financial Q3
and Rappor
financial Q4
in the
prompt
system,
my LLM
Vera
without
that the
userer
without that
the user
you have
access to
Rappor
Q3
and Q4
agent has
an
tool search
in
file,
he
makes with the
name
of the
file that
he has
in the
problem,
and the
question
he has
asked
and it
that
did
do
do you
and it
and that
that
repubber
the
little
And for
to
create
documents
type
canvas,
we
will
pass a
bit
quickly
there
for
to
leave
the
place
to
give
time
we're
there
we
do
write in
Convas
create
Convas,
of
of grep that
the
all
LLM
to
decry
to create
system,
so we have
have to create
two
new
new index,
those of
the artifacts
for stock
the
documents and
the chunk for
able to
do the rack
on the
this functionality
that's
any product
manager
appellate
totally
trivial.
Well,
the agentic
demar,
we're
commas
to create
the workflow
to assemble
the
super tools,
the problem is
very
we're in
that
has created Frankenstein,
and the
thing,
it's all the thing, in
all the whole
sense, in production
he's
not,
as we're not
as
we're supposed
to work,
and function,
on
on our
on, on, on,
on, on,
gere this problem,
and how
how
we're doing
what's
in the
workflow?
Before
all,
and at
at Chelastick,
they're
not you
the contrary,
it's that if
we
want to
understand something,
it
you know,
and that
if we
want
observe the
things,
you have
pre-pure
the
mechanisms for
capture
all the
data
that we have
used to
to qualify
the
thing to qualify the
So Ivan,
we've
we're
going to
a
on the
which we
pass
the
rag to
a
agent
conversational
to
the
construction
of
workflow
and it
the
same
manner
that at the
moment
to
pass
get the
to
the
question of the
good
structure
of the
data
for
not
information
and
to
start
as we
would.
At
At the time it was just
the generation
the message
there,
we have to be
the
question,
how is we need to
how is that we
to stocked the information of my
agents, for
to be able to
good
comportment,
calculate the
metrics that I
want to
the metrics that I
want to be the
it's a
can't
get an agent and
to make an
that's not due
simple.
So we're
going to
distinguish the workflows
where we're
doing an
enchantment of
tool and
the
appell of
LLM
that is
determinist
and me
metrised
of the
agents type
React
or the
LLLM
decides he
same
of the
actions to
effectue
after
actually the
agent
type
react
only,
we have
at a
pre-of-of-re
they
follow the
format
Open
AIII.
We can
decry
describe
all the run
of an
agent
React
like the
simple
list alternance
of
message
especially
the message
assistant
because the
agent
react is
turned
to turn
until
it
is
there
messages
assistants and
of
of the
tool to
the
response
final
should be
done.
But when we
want to
make
to marry
the
agents
react
and
make
things,
we're
on
how it's
define
a
workflow?
Finally,
we're
apply
the
rule of
if
something
looks
to
a canar
fesquick quick
like
a
canar,
it's
that it's
probably
a canar, it's probably
a
canar.
I suppose
that
many of
some
have done
in this
,
have
the
research
and when when I
and when I
have
a
image
on
your
on your
image
of the
N8N,
an
out of
on your
your
image of
an
exercise of
math
the
graph
acyclique,
with the
the
little
the little
of
image that
you
are
quite
it's
kind of
sometimes.
we
don't
so
we
want
so
we
decid
that we
represent
We can
can
represent
the workflow
workflow
of ya
asyclic,
asyclicic, and if
if we're
we're going to
get a cyclicicity
later when we're
going to
it's going to
it's a
graph, we can
define
as
these neus and
the
links that
that's
exactly
that we're
going to choose
for the
decry.
So, here
you have an
illustration of
our
tool for
create,
tool intern,
for
create
these workflows
in
no code and
they're
executed, we
have in
fact,
base
this
philosophy
of
workflow
as
the workflow like
graph
for
to be
that
we're
represent
the workflow
like
the
jison
which the
main
the
and then
we can
also
stock
the
list
of
later
and
the
execution
and each
each
contains
the
information
necessary and
sufficient to
execute
the
new
and
each
arret,
the
information
necessary and
sufficient
for
pass
the
of a
new
to
the
right,
so we can
think
Frank
Einstein,
like
I
know
it's
so
construct
and
code,
I'm
drag and drop the
different
the different
new,
I'm
connect, and
and then
then I
edit the
properties
of
each
it's
exactly that
part
of creation
of the
agent,
and then
you have
the
the part
of the
execution of
an agent,
one
once
that I'm
I'm
I'm content
of
my
run,
I'm
let
in
the
nature
and
And then then I
and then I
look
what he has
he has
these two
steps
that are
often
in the
but it's
concept of the
concept of
the
purpose in
Uytyn,
and that's
a year,
when I'm
once, he
he's
execute
with an
ID
of an
instante,
and then
he will
produce
the
point of
data that
that I
will
want
observe
to be sure
that
that all
to be sure
to be sure that
in other
other
on other
of my
logic
So finally
at
this
we have
decided that he
will not have
not we have
not have
a single
but two
index
for
to be able
to
capture
to capture
all
what
the
entire
of
our
So,
once
that we
have
the
information
on the
new
and
on the
execution
of an
agent
unitary
we can
reconstruct
all
so.
Finally
we
will
have
the index
of
workflows
that will
stocked
an
execution
unique of
a workflow
when
When I
I will
start for example, my workflow
that will me
will me explain the
the
with a
with plenty of
indicators
different,
I'll
let's a
instant
T, my
back-en is
in the
running the
he sov
the
ID unique
of run of
the
workflow, the
user, the
date of
the
the date of
fin,
is
he has
crashed in
in
plain
middle, or
is
he has
in
the
information
basic
on the
processus
on
the
processus,
, at
each
once
that I
advance
in my
workflow,
I
and I'm
going to stock
the trace
of the
of this
know,
what is
it has been
in
entry of the
new,
what is
being
in
out of
it's
that the
type of
new for that I
could be
able to
do
do the
re-produability
and to
relancet the
if it had
had been
a problem
like a
a crash
of API or
a problem
of the
the
problem of
LLM. And,
we
we're
found that with
these two
sole
structure of
we arrive,
to have
have
agent that
are stateful,
a
for
the
for the
which I
can
start
the
execution at
a
moment,
get the
back
and
because
the
information
stocked
in the
notes
are
necessary and
sufficient
for
re-execute
each
stage
of
the
point
that
that I
interest
and
that I
want
and that
and
why it's
extremely
prece
at
the
idea of the
I
Antic,
it's
because
it
to
have
a
control
on
my
data.
I can identify with
obviously a
work of
working with obviously a
logging,
can
be
automatized
with
other
agent,
where
my agent
has
in
production,
at
what
state
he has
he
had
and so
after
of
these
information
that, I
can
ameliorer
my agent
in production
and this
performance.
And that,
these
self-learning
agents,
the agents,
who will
are
progress
that they
launch in
production,
observe what
observe
and that
and that we
are
and that's
that's
it's possible,
that I
stock
firmly
and properly
the
trace
of all the
run that I
have
and that's
possible
with
only two
new
new index,
even
even if the
the list
to
be a
little long.
For you
distract
and redimized
a
we
propose a
little
demo of what
we
I've
got to
what you
Rassure
the
demo,
it's
I mean
don't
very
long
so it's
it's
soon,
so it
The
the
demo,
so in
that's the
kind of
application
that's
it was the
good time,
so it's
the
good time
of
the
dashboard,
with
d'
dimensions
that we
can
represent
issued
an ontology,
that we
present
so form
of barchart,
of
camamberr
the
of noh
noh of mow.
we.
We've also,
we have
there also,
these concepts
diverse and
various and varied,
the concept
of risk,
the concept of
security,
there,
these concepts
and then
that is
related by
the relations,
so the
both of
like the
relations
of
co-occurance,
and
or the
relations
in the
there's
phrase, there is
a
word transitive, that
so that's
the time
was a
quiet, and
now, and
it's
appeared
this thing
that is the
the agent,
in fact,
and the
idea
being
to have
an
interactivity
in language
natural,
and I
I'll put my
question,
my session.
And I can
you can
ask a
question
basic
So,
the list,
the
We'll
see
if you
see you
will
be the
question
that
was
used
by the
Russ.
So
so
hope,
my
connection
function,
it's
it will
respond.
So Elastic,
think,
already
finished.
So
The Retrieve is already parted.
And he mulein, it's a Gwynne 3, 32B, Bershemi, on a premise.
It's on these cards.
He's even not quantized, so he's on two cards 48 giga.
Okay, we've been a sort of a list, is what it's what it's worth.
Okay, and in fact, I find it incompletes.
So, I'm saying,
...
Ah, yeah, yeah, we.
And you have also the sourcing
amned by the RAC of all the documents of your base
used to you to provide this response.
The chunks are related to the documents,
and we can see where you get the things.
And you click it, it's all right?
So, add, the date of construction,
the constructor,
and the characteristic,
I tap like the police,
technique.
We're a table or we don't not a tableau?
No, no, we're not to demand a tableau.
No, no, we'll not demand a table.
So he mulein,
it, so he will reprint the conversation the
last tour in which I had described
that I would have a list,
so he'll be able,
we'll be able,
that he will reprimed my trick
and me complete.
My list
becomes a little more complicated,
and I've got a lot more
more of things
for each one of the entries
that I had before my poor entry.
Okay,
so he me,
he's about the T-90M-Arm,
Armata,
of the Proxif, the T-72, that's a little bitrapanel.
Hop, the 62,
even more, they've been re-sorted.
There, the Armata, we've had to have
talked.
I think we'll have launched for a moment,
there.
The Terminator.
Hop, the B-TMTMT,
well, you'll be maybe finish, no?
He's very prolix.
He'll be like to be l'er to be l'er at 104.
You see the necessity
to chunk the
tours of conversation?
Yeah, so at each time.
So it has finished.
It's right, the source.
So, well, I'm going to say,
the structure of my
you will have to
let me
say the same
thing
for the
Ukrainians.
So,
so he will
reprend
the tour of
conversation
before,
where I
said
that I'd
do you want
to
the structure of the list,
and he's
going to
me
and he's
part,
it.
It's all
there are
there are the
Abrams-S-American in
Yes,
because it's the
Russian
so we're
so
normally they're
there
so
So that
Mouline
I'm
my demo
it will not
not
very very long
it's
good,
let's
there's
I'm
there really a
a report 1-a-a-d
in
between the
all of the
index that
we have
it's a
so the
so I'm
it's
the same
same thing
the same thing
but for
for the
air of
and the Russian and the
So I'm
it's the
same
but for
the
avion
of the
and the
for the
russ
there's
so
they're
and I'm
will be able to
be able to
to be able to
we're
we can't
the
carmion,
and
So,
there's
I think that you
I'm
Well,
well,
after me,
there's a
there's
so there's
So,
they're
the geke
like the
for many of
these
these things,
there,
so,
there's
So,
flanker, and he
and he
he's even a conclusion.
So,
so the idea,
so the idea, is to
reprove the structure of the
conversation,
to reprove the
elements,
to know what
and to
conversation
fluid,
with a
partage of context,
communication
minimal at
a traffic,
so I'll let
conclude.
We're
we're going to
a conclusion.
I'm,
you're
you have convinced
this talk
that
arrive at
this interaction
natural and
fluid,
that
that you
seem so
if you
use
used
to be
on the
implementation
back-end that
but
you
that you
making,
that
the
new,
you're
, you know,
question,
final,
we can
,
is that the
idea of the
end of the
idea
,
in the
new kinds of
information that
the
complexity of
system that
is
a bit
reducter.
But, but,
the
fact,
of the
, and it's the
So,
when,
in the
we've
had
had been
and
we're
and it's
not
we're
we're not
and we're
things,
and
the
in an
uh...
they're
in the
user prompt
they were
with the
data
technically to
a fact,
and it
and it's
different
today.
our agent
to be able
to
to be
the
he has been
he
potentially
uh...
to
the
of the
other
and
etc.
And finally,
the art
of the
the
operation
is of
this operation
to effect
that operation of
that
Carpaty has
called context
engineering,
uh...
of the
with the
contract
the
time
of the
and the
and we're in
that
we can
the
information,
we can
they're
in the
different,
that's
that
the
presented.
all our
work
to organize the
and
the
and to organize the
performance of the
performance
that we
we're
the
take the
result of
and
information that
we're
that we're
the
New
new
state
of
the
ecosystem,
is that we
have
used to
the
LLLM,
in the
agent,
the
of
product
by the
PME
of Tech.
we're
delocalalal
like
the
model,
because
it's
but the
infrastructure
agentic
is
made
part
in the
same
title
that the
fronten
and the
offer that
will
now
propose
and
monetize
the
companies
of
tech.
And
when we
would
could
be
in
In 2022,
the question that
finally the
LLM
will be
ell-clipsed
the index,
the motors,
research,
visualizations and
they're
obsolete, this
new,
reconfiguration
of the
pageage of
the
tech in
2025,
the
motor of
research
like elastic
revien
even more
to
because
they
become the
the source of
all the
data that
will manipulate
the
agents
for
power
function
correctly.
Thank
of your attention.
Thank you.